{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"86.7/1.7",
			"answer":"86.7/1.7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.087/0.87",
			"answer":"0.087/0.87",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"89.1/0.99",
			"answer":"89.1/0.99",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"8.14/3.7",
			"answer":"8.14/3.7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.316/7.9",
			"answer":"0.316/7.9",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"154/7",
			"answer":"154/7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"3.24/4",
			"answer":"3.24/4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"96.6/6",
			"answer":"96.6/6",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.427/7",
			"answer":"0.427/7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"90/6",
			"answer":"90/6",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}

	]
}